<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aplicación de prueba de terror</string>
    <string name="q1Text">Estás perdido en un cementerio a medianoche, solo. Y ves una figura alta entre los shodaws mirándote con ojos blancos. A qué te dedicas (1</string>
    <string name="q2Text">Si escuchas unos golpecitos en tu ventana por la noche y te giras y ves una figura mirándote, ¿qué harás? (2</string>
    <string name="q3text">Hay un hombre siguiéndote y cuando comienzas a caminar rápido y él comienza a correr hacia ti, ¿cuál es tu próximo movimiento? (3</string>
    <string name="q4text">Estás atrapado en una cabaña con dos personajes famosos de películas de terror: Jason Voorhees de Viernes 13 y Freddy Krueger de Pesadilla en Elm Street. Tienes que elegir uno al que enfrentarte, sabiendo que puedes sobrevivir. (4</string>
    <string name="q5text">Estás deambulando por la campiña de Texas cuando te encuentras con Leatherface de La masacre de Texas. ¿Ves dos formas de escapar? (5</string>
    <string name="q6text">¿Te despiertas encadenado en una habitación oscura y Jigsaw** de Saw* te ofrece cuatro opciones para escapar? (6</string>
    <string name="q7Text">Estás atrapado en un hotel espeluznante y Jack Torrance de The Shining te persigue con un hacha. ¿Ves 4 posibles salidas? (7</string>
    <string name="q8Text">Te encuentras en una zona rural donde The Creeper de Jeepers Creepers está buscando a su próxima víctima. ¿Tienes dos formas de escapar? (8</string>
    <string name="q9Text">Estás en una casa embrujada y The Babadook acecha en las sombras. ¿Tienes dos opciones para sobrevivir? (9</string>
    <string name="q10Text">El Depredador te está acechando en una densa jungla. Tienes dos opciones para sobrevivir? (10</string>
    <string name="q1ChoiceA">Acércate a la figura para preguntarle si puede ayudarte a encontrar el camino.</string>
    <string name="q1ChoiceB">Corre en la dirección opuesta lo más rápido que puedas.</string>
    <string name="q1ChoiceC">Quédate completamente quieto y observa la figura por un momento.</string>
    <string name="q1ChoiceD">Llame a la figura, tratando de comunicarse.</string>
    <string name="q2ChoiceA">Abre la ventana para ver qué quiere la figura.</string>
    <string name="q2ChoiceB">Apaga las luces y escóndete debajo de la cama.</string>
    <string name="q2ChoiceC">Grab your phone to call for help.</string>
    <string name="q2ChoiceD">Stay silent and watch the figure closely.</string>
    <string name="q3ChoiceA">Corre en la dirección opuesta lo más rápido que puedas.</string>
    <string name="q3ChoiceB">Turn around and confront him, asking what he wants.</string>
    <string name="q3ChoiceC">Look for a nearby place to hide, like a store or alley.</string>
    <string name="q3ChoiceD">Yell for help to attract attention.</string>
    <string name="q4ChoiceA">Face Jason Voorhees in the cabin</string>
    <string name="q4ChoiceB">Confront Freddy Krueger in your dreams</string>
    <string name="q4ChoiceC">Try to escape the cabin through a window</string>
    <string name="q4ChoiceD">" Attempt to negotiate with one of them for your life."</string>
    <string name="q5ChoiceA">Hide in a nearby thicket of trees</string>
    <string name="q5ChoiceB">Climb a fence to get to a neighboring property</string>
    <string name="q5ChoiceC">Try to reason with Leatherface, hoping he’ll let you go</string>
    <string name="q5ChoiceD">Run down the open dirt road where you might find help.</string>
    <string name="q6ChoiceA">Solve a series of puzzles he has laid out for you</string>
    <string name="q6ChoiceB">Attempt to break the chains using any nearby tools</string>
    <string name="q6ChoiceC">Follow the instructions of a recorded message from Jigsaw</string>
    <string name="q6ChoiceD">Call out for help, hoping someone will hear you.</string>
    <string name="q7ChoiceA">" The emergency exit door down the hall."</string>
    <string name="q7ChoiceB">The snow-covered maze outside.</string>
    <string name="q7ChoiceC">A window you could break to escape.</string>
    <string name="q7ChoiceD">A staircase leading to the upper floors.</string>
    <string name="q8ChoiceA">Hide in a nearby barn and wait for him to leave.</string>
    <string name="q8ChoiceB">Try to find a vehicle and drive away.</string>
    <string name="q8ChoiceC">Climb onto the roof of a house to get a better vantage point.</string>
    <string name="q8ChoiceD">Run into the dense woods to find shelter.</string>
    <string name="q9ChoiceA">Confront The Babadook and try to reason with it.</string>
    <string name="q9ChoiceB">Find a way to banish it using items from the house</string>
    <string name="q9ChoiceC">Hide in a closet and stay silent.</string>
    <string name="q9ChoiceD">Search for a way out through the back door</string>
    <string name="q10ChoiceA">Cover yourself in ,ud to mask your heat signature</string>
    <string name="q10ChoiceB">Hide in the trees and stay silent</string>
    <string name="q10ChoiceC">Set traps using vine and rocks</string>
    <string name="q10ChoiceD">Run around yelling like a fool</string>
    <string name="correct_msg">You Got it Correct</string>
    <string name="wrong_msg">loser you got it wrong</string>
    <string name="pointmsg">you have lost a point</string>
</resources>