<resources>
    <string name="app_name">horrorQuizApp</string>
    <string name="q1Text">You\'re lost in a grave yard at midnight all by yourself. And you see a tall figure in the shodaws looking at you with white eyes. What do you do (1</string>
    <string name="q2Text">If you hear tapping on your window at night and turn to see a figure looking at you what will you do? (2</string>
    <string name="q3text">There’s a man following you and as you start to walk fast and he starts running at you, what\'s your next move? (3</string>
    <string name="q4text">You’re trapped in a cabin with two famous horror movie characters: Jason Voorhees from Friday the 13th and Freddy Krueger from A Nightmare on Elm Street. You have to choose one to face, knowing you may survive (4</string>
    <string name="q5text">You’re wandering through the Texas countryside when you encounter Leatherface from The Texas Chainsaw Massacre. You spot two ways to escape? (5</string>
    <string name="q6text">You wake up chained in a dark room, and Jigsaw** fromSaw* gives you four choices to escape? (6</string>
    <string name="q7Text">You’re stuck in a creepy hotel, and Jack Torrance from The Shining is coming after you with an axe. You see 4 possible exits? (7</string>
    <string name="q8Text">You find yourself in a rural area where The Creeper from Jeepers Creepers is hunting for his next victim. You have two ways to escape? (8</string>
    <string name="q9Text">You’re in a haunted house, and The Babadook is lurking in the shadows. You have two options to survive? (9</string>
    <string name="q10Text">You’re being stalked by The Predator in a dense jungle. You have two options for survival? (10</string>
    <string name="q1ChoiceA">Approach the figure to ask if they can help you find your way (A</string>
    <string name="q1ChoiceB">Run in the opposite direction as fast as you can. (B</string>
    <string name="q1ChoiceC">Stay completely still and observe the figure for a moment (C</string>
    <string name="q1ChoiceD">Call out to the figure, trying to communicate. (D</string>
    <string name="q2ChoiceA">Open the window to see what the figure wants (A</string>
    <string name="q2ChoiceB">Turn off the lights and hide under the bed. (B</string>
    <string name="q2ChoiceC">Grab your phone to call for help. (C</string>
    <string name="q2ChoiceD">Stay silent and watch the figure closely.(D</string>
    <string name="q3ChoiceA">" Run in the opposite direction as fast as you can" (A</string>
    <string name="q3ChoiceB">Turn around and confront him, asking what he wants. (B</string>
    <string name="q3ChoiceC">Look for a nearby place to hide, like a store or alley. (C</string>
    <string name="q3ChoiceD">Yell for help to attract attention. (D</string>
    <string name="q4ChoiceA">Face Jason Voorhees in the cabin (A</string>
    <string name="q4ChoiceB">Confront Freddy Krueger in your dreams (B</string>
    <string name="q4ChoiceC">Try to escape the cabin through a window (C</string>
    <string name="q4ChoiceD">Attempt to negotiate with one of them for your life. (D</string>
    <string name="q5ChoiceA">Hide in a nearby thicket of trees (A</string>
    <string name="q5ChoiceB">Climb a fence to get to a neighboring property (B</string>
    <string name="q5ChoiceC">Try to reason with Leatherface, hoping he’ll let you go (C</string>
    <string name="q5ChoiceD">Run down the open dirt road where you might find help. (D</string>
    <string name="q6ChoiceA">Solve a series of puzzles he has laid out for you (A</string>
    <string name="q6ChoiceB">Attempt to break the chains using any nearby tools (B</string>
    <string name="q6ChoiceC">Follow the instructions of a recorded message from Jigsaw (C</string>
    <string name="q6ChoiceD">Call out for help, hoping someone will hear you. (D</string>
    <string name="q7ChoiceA">" The emergency exit door down the hall." (A</string>
    <string name="q7ChoiceB">The snow-covered maze outside. (B</string>
    <string name="q7ChoiceC">A window you could break to escape. (C</string>
    <string name="q7ChoiceD">A staircase leading to the upper floors. (D</string>
    <string name="q8ChoiceA">Hide in a nearby barn and wait for him to leave. (A</string>
    <string name="q8ChoiceB">Try to find a vehicle and drive away. (B</string>
    <string name="q8ChoiceC">Climb onto the roof of a house to get a better vantage point. (C</string>
    <string name="q8ChoiceD">Run into the dense woods to find shelter. (D</string>
    <string name="q9ChoiceA">Confront The Babadook and try to reason with it. (A</string>
    <string name="q9ChoiceB">Find a way to banish it using items from the house (B</string>
    <string name="q9ChoiceC">Hide in a closet and stay silent. (C</string>
    <string name="q9ChoiceD">Search for a way out through the back door (D</string>
    <string name="q10ChoiceA">Cover yourself in ,ud to mask your heat signature (A</string>
    <string name="q10ChoiceB">Hide in the trees and stay silent (B</string>
    <string name="q10ChoiceC">Set traps using vine and rocks (C</string>
    <string name="q10ChoiceD">Run around yelling like a fool (D</string>
    <string name="correct_msg">You Got it Correct</string>
    <string name="wrong_msg">you got it wrong</string>
    <string name="pointmsg">you have lost a point</string>
</resources>